Sasu Luhtala

CONTACT

+358 504054707 sluhtala@me.com Hiihtäjäntie 2A, 00810 Helsinki

SKILLS

C C++ PHP Python Javascript

React Node.js SQL HTML CSS Git

Blender3D Unity Unreal Engine Adobe products Clear Communication Juggling

LANGUAGES

Finnish (native) English

PROFILE

I'm 27 years old. I'm looking for an internship opportunity to gain experience in the technology industry. I have a background as a designer, so I consider to be good at critical thinking and problem solving. Currently I study at coding school Hive Helsinki and I'm interested in backend, AI, algorhithms, graphics

EDUCATION

Tikkakoski upper secondary school (2009-2012)

Tampere University of applied sciences (2013 – 2018)

Hive Helsinki (2019 - current)

RELATED WORK EXPERIENCE

ADDITIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Concept designer at Plotwise Inc. (01/2016 – 05/2017)

A visual design work for a film-preproduction / VFX - company. The job involved concept art, storyboarding, matte-painting and illustration for films and television series.

Work Try-out media-workshop at city of Tampere (07/2018 - 12/2018)

The job was about helping different service on media-related problems such designing and filming advertisement and filming streams.

Personal Project, 3D Animation (08/2016 - 05/2017)

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pufYOXVdJz0. I spent months with a friend doing this fun project. He handled the animation while I was responsible for the technical aspects of Blender3D.

Website: https://sluhtala.github.io

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sasu-luhtala-4abb7885

Github: https://github.com/sluhtala